Aminreza Hajiasgari

2325 Kansas Avenue Unit 8, Santa Monica, CA 90404

(310) 866-6386 aminreza.h@icloud.com

IT Technology Specialist with 4+ years of professional experience in technical trouble shooting, help desk, and web design.

Comprehensive knowledge in a wide variety of editing and design operating system software. Bachelor of Arts Degree in Information Technology.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

MCITP: Microsoft Certified IT Professional CCNA, Network +, Microsoft windows product and design and network maintenance

WordPress: Web design, create database, maintenance, slider design, search engine optimization, various social networks

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere, Avid, Final Cut Pro: Visual editing and design with picture and motions

Windows Servers, Linux Ubuntu and Fedora, Mac OS: Work with different operating systems

Social Media Marketing: Assist startups in branding, sourcing and marketing

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Lavan Ertebat Company

Management Information System, Desktop Engineer

Tehran, Iran
July 2012 - June 2016

- Troubleshooting system and network problems
- Install and configure computer hardware operating systems and applications
- Design and Modify WordPress Website
- Design promotional banners/business-cards for show-room display
- Market other technology-based activities.
- Antivirus installation to all desktops and laptops
- Provide support for MAC and PC Other
- Set up new users' accounts and profiles and dealing with password issues

Network Experts

Web Designer, Help desk, Digital advertisement designer

Remote desktop and troubleshooting

Beverly Hills, CA

October 2017 - Present

- Web designer and Help desk
- Computer services repair service
- Cabling Network and Installing computers and servers
- Online and offline advertisement
- Design and create advertisement via photoshop
- Design mapping and routing for smart home via Visio

Children Fun Dental Zone (West LA)

Social Media Editor Los Angeles, CA

• Video and Picture Editor June 2018 - Present

EDUCATION

UCLA Extension - Currently Enrolled in Social Media Marketing, Video Editing

Azad University, Tehran, Iran - Bachelor of Arts in Information Technology (IT) Engineering, December 2016

LANGUAGES

Fluent in Farsi and English